Finding Aid for the Edward C. Weber Papers, 1949-2005
Edward C. Weber Papers
- Correspondence
  - Borrowed Times (Missoula, MT) (Box 8)
  - Boss (New York) (Box 8)
  - Boston Public Library (Box 8)
  - Boston, Raymond J. (reference: John Francis Bray) (Box 8)
  - Botero, Ebel (Box 8)
  - Bottum, Olivia (Box 8)
  - Bouchier, David (reference: New Left, ecology, women’s movement) (Box 8)
  - Boulware, Marcus (reference: Lucy Thurman, Women’s Christian Temperance Union) (Box 8)
  - Bound Together (San Francisco) (Box 8)
  - Bowling Green State University (Box 8)
  - Boyd, Melba (Box 8)
  - Brademas, John (U.S. Representative) (Box 8)
  - Bradford, Rod (reference: D.M. Bennett, Josephine Tilton, Stephen Pearl Andrews) (Box 8)
  - Bradshaw, James A. (Box 8)
  - Bradshaw, James Stanford (Box 8)
  - Brady, Marcelino Flanter (re: universal homosexual rights-Santiago, Chile) (Box 8)
  - Branch, Ed (reference: James T. Farrell) (Box 8)
  - Brand (Sweden) (Box 8)
  - Brand, Benjamin (Emma Goldman’s essay, “Herschel Feibel Grynspan and his Tormentors”) (Box 8)
  - Brandt, Charlton J. (reference: Syndicalist League of North America; Jay Fox; William Z. Foster) (Box 8)
  - Bratach Dubh (Anarchist publishers - Scotland) (Box 8)
  - Brazier, Richard D. (reference: Little Red Songbook) (Box 8)
  - Breakout! Collective. (London) (Box 8)
  - Breitbart, Myrra (reference: Boletín de Información) (Box 8)
  - Breslow, Lori (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 8)
  - Breton, R. Yves ( Krach – Montreal) (Box 8)
  - Brewer, David Whitney (Box 8)
  - Brick (AL) (Box 8)
  - Bridge (Chicago) (Box 8)
  - Brinkley, Alan (reference: Charles E. Coughlin, Huey Long) (Box 8)
  - British Anarchism Survey (Martyn Everett) (reference: E.T. Craig, Ambrose Cuddon, Henry Seymour, Charlotte Watson) (Box 8)
  - British Columbia Federation of Labor (reference: B.C. IWW) (Box 8)
  - British Council of Churches (Box 8)
  - Broadsheet (Australia) (Box 8)
  - Broadside/Free Press (Cambridge, MA) (Box 8)
  - Broadside Press (Detroit) (Box 8)
  - Brock, Kenneth D. (Box 8)
  - Brockway, Darrell (reference: Daniel DeLeon) (Box 8)
  - Broderick, William D. (donation) (Box 8)
  - Broken Arrow (Detroit) (Box 8)
  - Brook, Michael (reference: Swedish-American radicalism) (Box 8)
  - Brooks, Anna Marie (reference: Frederick William Roman, Utopian Society (Box 8)
  - Brooks, Frank H. (reference: Dyer D. Lum (Box 8)
  - Brother (Berkeley, CA) (Box 8)
  - Brown, Charles C. (reference: review of Jack Lively book on Alexis de Tocqueville) (Box 8)
  - Brown, David (Left Bank Books/Black Eye Press) (Box 8)
  - Brown, F. (Box 8)
  - Brown, Jay and Peggy (Box 8)
  - Brown, M. R. (reference: Ben Fletcher) (Box 8)
  - Brown, Melvin P. (re: donation of Lyndon LaRouche materials) (Box 8)
  - Brown, Ruth and Jim (4 folders) (Box 9)
  - Brownstone, The (New York) (Box 9)
  - Bruccoli, Matthew (reference: Sanctuary) (Box 9)
  - Brundage Hill Research Publications (re: Black Lesbian Bibliography) (Box 9)
  - Brunson, Isaiah (Brooklyn CORE) (Box 9)
  - Bubka, Tony (reference: Harlan County Coal Strike; Ralph Chaplain stickers) (Box 9)
  - Buchanan, Patrick J. ( From the Right) (Box 9)
  - Buchstein, Fred (reference: Josiah Warren) (Box 9)
  - Buckingham, Peter H. (reference: Frank P. O’Hare) (Box 9)
  - Buckley, John M. (reference: William D. Haywood) (Box 9)
  - Bufe, Chaz (Box 9)
  - Buffalo Gay Services (Box 9)
  - Bugle, The (Milwaukee) (Box 9)
  - Buhle, Paul (Box 9)
  - Bulletin Intérieur (France) (Box 9)
  - Bulletin [of International Socialism] (New York) (Box 9)
  - Bulletin of Anarchist Research (Tom Cahill) (Box 9)
  - Bulletin Publications (New York) (Box 9)
  - Burgmann, Verity N. (reference: Australia IWW) (Box 9)
  - Burke, Storey (Box 9)
  - Burkland, Edna (Box 9)
  - Burley, Laurel (reference: POUM) (Box 9)
  - Burmese Relief Centre (Box 9)
  - Burning Spear (Ann Arbor) (Box 9)
  - Burros, R. (Proletarian Party Press) (Box 9)
  - Burrows, Kenneth David (reference: Sacco and Vanzetti) (Box 9)
  - Business Media Resources (reference: images of immigrants for An American Portfolio) (Box 9)
  - Butler, Susan (Box 9)
  - Butts, Charles L. (re: Mississippi Free Press) (Box 9)
  - CERMTRI (Paris) (Box 9)
  - C.H.E. (Campaign for Homosexual Equality – England) (Box 9)
  - C.I.O News (Washington DC) (Box 9)
  - C.I.O.-U.A.W. (Box 9)
  - C.I.R.A. (Centre International de Recherches sur l’Anarchisme) (Box 9)
  - C.L.G.H. Newsletter (Annandale-on-Hudson, New York) (Box 9)
  - C.N.T. (Box 9)
  - COFFLA (Common Front for Latin America) (Maryland) (Box 9)
  - COSMEP (Committee of Small Magazines and Publishers) (Box 9)
  - C.V.M. Newsletter (Council for Voluntary Military) (Chicago) (Box 9)
  - Cage and the Doorkey, The (California) (Box 9)
  - Cahiers des Amis de Han Ryner (Box 9)
  - Cahiers de L’Humanisme Libertaire (Paris) (Box 9)
  - Cahn, William (reference: American labor history, Richard Trevellick) (Box 9)
  - Cain, Frank M. (reference: IWW photographs) (Box 9)
  - Cain, James W. (donation) (Box 9)
  - Cakwebe, Duke C. (Box 9)
  - Calderon, Francine (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn) (Box 9)
  - Caldwell, J. T. (The Strickland Press, Guy Aldred, No Traitors’ Gait) (Box 9)
  - California Black Rose ( Bicicleta) (Box 9)
  - California Socialist (Los Angeles) (Box 9)
  - California State University (Fullerton) (Box 9)
  - Call, Jack (Metaphrast of the Emanations & Chief of Protocol) (Box 9)
  - Callaloo (Lexington, KY) (Box 9)
  - Camacho Escamez, Diego (reference: Emma Goldman, Buenaventura Durruti) (Box 9)
  - Camp, Helen C. (reference: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn) (Box 9)
  - Campbell, Tim ( GLC Voice) (Box 9)
  - Camp Ink (Campaign Against Moral Persecution) (Australia) (Box 9)
  - Camp News (Chicago) (Box 9)
  - Campaign for a Democratic Foreign Policy (Box 9)
  - Campaigner, The (National Caucus of Labor Committees) (New York) (Box 10)
  - Campos, Martha (Donation; see SVF: Labor – U.S. – Mergers – Gulf Oil Company) (Box 10)
  - Canadian Gay Archives (Toronto) (Box 10)
  - Canadian Lesbian and Gay Rights Coalition ( NGRC) (Ottowa) (Box 10)
  - Canadian Women’s Educational Press (Toronto) (Box 10)
  - Candour:The British Views-Letter (London) (Box 10)
  - Cantine-Wohlfahrt, Thérèse (Box 10)
  - Cantsin, Elliot (Box 10)
  - Capital Voice, The (Washington DC) (Box 10)
  - Caplan, Ron (reference: Alexander Berkman) (Box 10)
  - Capsule News (Arlington, VA) (Box 10)
  - Caracol (San Antonio, TX) (Box 10)
  - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation ( Mindszenty Report) (St. Louis) (Box 10)
  - Carey, Dennis P. (reference: J. William Loyd) (Box 10)
  - Carey, Kevin (Box 10)
  - Carey, Peter (Box 10)
  - Caribbé (Philadelphia) (Box 10)
  - Caribbean Workers Weekly (London) (Box 10)
  - Carillon, The (Saskatchewan) (Box 10)
  - Carlson, Andrew R. (reference: German radicals and newspapers) (Box 10)
  - Carlson, Peter (reference: William D. Haywood) (Box 10)
  - Carolina Plain Dealer (Durham, NC) (Box 10)
  - Carpenter, Karen (reference: Women in the IWW) (Box 10)
  - Carr, Mary M. (Box 10)
  - Carr, Robert ( Smurfs in Hell) (Box 10)
  - Carroll, Celeste (Box 10)
  - Carson, Robe (reference: Journal of Orgonomy) (Box 10)
  - Cary, Michael D. (reference: MC5, White Panther Party) (Box 10)
  - Casciato, Art (reference: League of American Writers) (Box 10)
  - Casey, Anne (Box 10)
  - Cash, Harvey (reference: Casa Reports) (Box 10)
  - Cashin, Richard (re: donation) (Box 10)
  - Caswell, Lucy S. (reference: general) (Box 10)
  - Catalyst (Culver City, CA) (Box 10)
  - Catalyst (Exeter, England) (Box 10)
  - Catanese, Lynn Ann (reference: Emma Goldman; conscription) (Box 10)
  - Catholic Worker (New York) (Box 10)
  - Cavalier (Mount Morris, IL) (Box 10)
  - Cawood, Richard (complaint about Labadie Collection’s hours of service) (Box 10)
  - Cazden, Robert (reference: German-American radicalism) (Box 10)
  - Center, Don B. (reference: general) (Box 10)
  - Center for Educational Productions (reference: making a documentary film on IWW) (Box 10)
  - Center for Information on Latin America ( Grito y Fusil) (Box 10)
  - Center for Inquiry (Paul Kurtz) (Box 10)
  - Center for Libertarian Studies (Box 10)
  - Center for Research Libraries (CRL) (Box 10)
  - Center for Rural Studies ( People and Land) (Box 10)
  - Center for Socialist History ( CSH Interbulletin) (Box 10)
  - Center for United Labor Action (Box 10)
  - Center for the Study of Armament and Disarmament (Box 10)
  - Center for the Study of Popular Culture (Letter from ECW to David Horowitz – no reply) (Box 10)
  - Central American Peace & Democracy Watch Bulletin (Washington DC) (Box 10)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors (Box 10)
  - Central Distribution (Oakland, CA) (Box 10)
  - Centre de Documentació Histórico-Social (Barcelona) (Box 10)
  - Centro D’Iniziativa Gay (Milano) (Box 10)
  - Centro Documentazione Anarchica (Box 10)
  - Centro Studi Libertari “G. Pinelli” (Milano) (Box 10)
  - Century Books, Inc. (Box 10)
  - Cerne, Lisa (reference: women in the Civil Rights Movement) (Box 10)
  - Chadwyck-Healey (Box 10)
  - Challenge/Desafio (New York) (Box 10)
  - Chamberlin, Brewster S. (reference: Knights of Labor Yearbook 1891) (Box 10)
  - Champion, Michael (Box 10)
  - Chapel Hill Freedom Committee (Box 10)
  - Chatfield, E. Charles (reference: pacifism) (Box 10)
  - Chavis, John (Curator, Education Division, Detroit Historical Museum) (reference: Joseph Labadie) (Box 10)
  - Chelsea House Publishers (reference: photos of Emma Goldman) (Box 10)
  - Chenoweth, Donald J. (reference: New International) (Box 11)
  - Cherny, Robert W. (reference: Harry Bridges) (Box 11)
  - Chersi, Andrea (reference: Robert Reitzel) (Box 11)
  - Chicago Public Library (Box 11)
  - Chicago Seed (Box 11)
  - Chicano Publications ( El Chicano) (Box 11)
  - Chile Solidarity Committee ( For a Free Chile) (Box 11)
  - China Rights Annals (Armonk, NY) (Box 11)
  - Chinese Information Service (Box 11)
  - Ching, Erik (reference: El Salvador 1900-11940) (Box 11)
  - Chosen Books (Box 11)
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade (Box 11)
  - Christian Crusade (Tulsa) (Box 11)
  - Christian Economics (Buena Park, CA) (Box 11)
  - Christian Renewal (Sussex, England) (Box 11)
  - Christian Vanguard (Hollywood) (Box 11)
  - Chronicle of Current Events (New York) (Box 11)
  - Chroniques des strategies présentes (France) (Box 11)
  - Church & State (Silver Spring, MD) (Box 11)
  - Church of the Christian Crusade (Charles Secrest) (Box 11)
  - Church League of America (Box 11)
  - Church of Eternal Life & Liberty ( Live and Let Live) (Box 11)
  - Churchill, Tom (reference: Eugene Barnett; Centralia) (Box 11)
  - Churchill, Marilyn (Southern Tenant Famer’s Union) (Box 11)
  - Cinema Educational Guild, Inc. (Box 11)
  - Citizen News (San Francisco) (Box 11)
  - Citizens Committee for a Free Cuba (Box 11)
  - Citizens Councils of America ( The Citizen) (Jackson, MS) (Box 11)
  - Citizens Report (Metairie, LA) (Box 11)
  - Civil Disorder Research Institute ( Civil Disorder Digest) (Box 11)
  - Civilisation Libertaire (Paris) (Box 11)
  - Claeys, Gregory (reference: Chartist Tracts for the Times, Josiah Warren, John Francis Bray) (Box 11)
  - Clark, Carolyn C. (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Clark, Norman (reference: Everett, IWW) (Box 11)
  - Clark, Thomas (reference: right-wing political speeches) (Box 11)
  - Class Struggle (October League) (Bell Gardens, CA) (Box 11)
  - Class War (London) (Box 11)
  - Clayton, Melford W. (reference: general) (Box 11)
  - Clements, Joyce M. (reference: 1934 San Francisco General Strike) (Box 11)
  - Clydeside Anarchists (Glasgow, Scotland) (Box 11)
  - Coal Miners Research Project (Box 11)
  - Coday, William (4 folders) (Box 11)
  - Coe, Kate (reference: bombing of A. Mitchell Palmer’s house) (Box 12)
  - Coffin, Jean-Christophe (reference: Italian immigrants) (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Carl (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Irving R. (reference: Charles Erskine Scott Wood) (Box 12)
  - Cohen, Ronald D. (reference: political folk music recordings (Box 12)
  - Colarocco, Pasquale (bust of Carlo Tresca requested by ECW) (Box 12)
  - Colby, David C. (reference: gay politics and the media) (Box 12)
  - Cole, Terry W. (reference: George F. Vanderveer and the IWW) (Box 12)
  - Colectivo de Concientizacion Gay (Puerto Rico) (Box 12)
  - Collart, Yves M. (reference: French radical immigrants) (no reply) (Box 12)
  - Collector’s Network, ALA (Box 12)
  - Colman, Sam (Box 12)
  - Columbia University Library (Box 12)
  - Combat (New York) (Box 12)
  - Come Out (New York) (Box 12)
  - Come Together (London) (Box 12)
  - Comegys, Robert G. (reference: Freethought: a Liberal Journal) (Box 12)
  - Comité d’Urgence Anti-Répression Homosexuelle (CUARH) (Paris) (Box 12)
  - Comité pro Presos de España (New York) (Box 12)
  - Comment (London) (Box 12)
  - Committee Against Violations of Human Rights in El Salvador (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain ( Spain Today) (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee for Freedom in Mozambique, Angola, and Guine (London) (Box 12)
  - Committee for Nonviolent Action (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee for the Free World ( Contentions) (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee of Ten Million (Norborne, MO) (Box 12)
  - Committee of U.S. Bolsheviks (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee on the Name Negro (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee to Aid the Monroe Defendants (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee to Defend Francisco Molina (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee to Protest Absurd Censorship (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell (New York) (Box 12)
  - Committee to Support the Revolution in Iran (Wayne State University) (Box 12)
  - Committees of Correspondence (Box 12)
  - Common Sense (Washington DC) (Box 12)
  - Communist Viewpoint (Toronto) (Box 12)
  - Communist Workers Party ( Workers Viewpoint) (Box 12)
  - Community Research and Action group ( Community) (Manchester, England) (Box 12)
  - Community Times (West Lafayette, IN) (Box 12)
  - Comunidad (Stockholm) (Box 12)
  - Comunidad de Orgullo Gay (Puerto Rico) (Box 12)
  - Comunidad Ibérica (Mexico) (Box 12)
  - Conari Press (reference: Mother Jones) (Box 12)
  - Confidencial (Costa Rica) (Box 12)
  - Congdon, Kirby ( Magazine 6) (Box 12)
  - Conlin, Joseph R. (reference: William D. Haywood, IWW) (Box 12)
  - Connections (Madison) (Box 12)
  - Conservative Viewpoint (Washington DC) (Box 12)
  - Constitution (New York) (reference: IWW (Box 12)
  - Constitutional Alliance, Inc. (Lansing) (Box 12)
  - Consumption (Seattle) (Box 12)
  - Contemporary Issues (London) (Box 12)
  - Conyers, John, Jr. (re: Vietnam War) (Box 12)
  - Cooke, Epsey M. (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 12)
  - Copeland, Tom (reference: Wesley Everest; Centralia; IWW) (Box 12)
  - COQ (Copenhagen) (Box 12)
  - Cork Workers Club (Ireland) (Box 12)
  - Cornell University – Dept. of Manuscripts and University Archives (reference: Henry Bool) (Box 12)
  - Cornell University – New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 12)
  - Cornford, Daniel (reference: Western Watchman) (Box 12)
  - Cornish, R. S. (reference: John Beverly Robinson) (Box 12)
  - Cornuault, J. (Box 12)
  - Coughlin, Michael E. (Box 12)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression (Box 12)
  - Council for the Defense of Freedom (Box 12)
  - Council of American-Soviet Friendship (Box 12)
  - Council of Federated Organizations (COFO) (Box 12)
  - Council(s) on Religion and the Homosexual (Box 12)
  - Councilor, The (Shreveport, LA) (Box 12)
  - Count Down (Wichita, KS) (Box 12)
  - Counterdraft (Los Angeles) (Box 12)
  - Counterpoint (Box 12)
  - Country Women (Albion, CA) (Box 12)
  - Court TV (reference: Roseberg-Sobell Case) (Box 12)
  - Cowan, Geoffery (reference: LA Times bombing, McNamara brothers, Clarence Darrow) (no reply) (Box 12)
  - Cowell, Sidney (reference: Clara Cowell) (Box 12)
  - Cox, Marion (Mr.) (reference: Morals vs. Art by Anthony Comstock) (Box 12)
  - Coy, Patrick G. (reference: Christian Anarchism) (Box 12)
  - Cozzie, Eugene O. (sale of materials from 1969 sit-in at University of Chicago) (Box 12)
  - Crazie (New York) (Box 12)
  - Creswell, Stephen (reference: Mississippi Socialist Party) (Box 12)
  - Crichton, Kevin John (reference: Nazi Party in Thuringia) (Box 12)
  - Crisálida (Guadalajara, Mexico) (Box 13)
  - Criterion, The (Honolulu, HI) (Box 13)
  - Crompton, Lewis (Lincoln-Omaha Council on Religion and the Homosexual) (Box 13)
  - Cross & the Flag, The (Box 13)
  - Crow, Suzanne, J. (reference: 1964 Freedom Summer; Project Mississippi; Edward L. Koch) (Box 13)
  - Crowley, Louise (Provos) (Box 13)
  - Crucible, The (Duluth, MN) (Box 13)
  - Crusader (Denham Springs, LA) (KKK) (Box 13)
  - Crusader (North Carolina) (Box 13)
  - Cuadernos de Formacion e Interpretacion Libertaria (Spain) (Box 13)
  - Cuba, Ministerio de Industrias (Box 13)
  - Cuba Socialista (Havana, Cuba) (Box 13)
  - Cuban-American National Foundation (Box 13)
  - Cuban Historical Trust (Box 13)
  - Cugini, Joseph (reference: American and British labor culture) (Box 13)
  - Culpepper, Betty (reference: John Birch Society, Julia Brown, George Schuyler) (Box 13)
  - Culter, Lois (reference: Spanish Civil War, AIT Plenums) (Box 13)
  - Cummings, Mary V. (reference: Henry and Elizabeth Vincent) (Box 13)
  - Cunliffe, David ( Global Tapestry) (re: Anarchist publications in England) (Box 13)
  - Cunneen, Chris (reference: Ragnar Redbeard, Arthur Desmond, Richard Thurland, Eagle and the Serpent, Lion’s Paw) (Box 13)
  - Cunningham, Hyacinth ( Befreiung) (anarchists visiting from Germany) (Box 13)
  - Cunningham, Dr. Valentine (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 13)
  - Cusick, Lois (reference: Spanish Civil War) (Box 13)
  - Cutler, Barry (Paedophile Information Exchange) (Kent, England) (Box 13)
  - Cyclamen Books (1) (England) (Box 13)
  - Cyclamen Books (2) (England) (Box 13)
  - Dabakis, Melissa (reference: Haymarket, Waldheim Cemetery, Pioneer Aid and Support Society) (Box 13)
  - Dahl, Frank A. (reference: Moscow Daily News) (Box 13)
  - Dahlen, Gladys L. (reference: Joe Hill song) (Box 13)
  - Dahlmann, Dittmar (reference: Makhno movement) (Box 13)
  - Daily Planet (Coconut Grove, FL) (Box 13)
  - Daily World, The (New York) (Box 13)
  - Daitz, Howard C. (offering glass-plate negatives of Trotsky, Lenin, etc.) (Box 13)
  - Daley, Richard M. (Mayor of Chicago) (Box 13)
  - D’Allante, Davina (Box 13)
  - Dallas Historical Society (reference: Albert Brisbane) (Box 13)
  - Dallas Notes (Box 13)
  - Darch, Colin (reference: foreign language anarchist newspapers) (Box 13)
  - Darling, Dick (Box 13)
  - Dart Bulletin (Red Bank, NJ) (Box 13)
  - Dartmouth College Library (reference: Underground press, Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, IWW) (Box 13)
  - Dartmouth Review (NH) (Box 13)
  - Das Anarchiv (Frankfurt, Germany) (Box 13)
  - D’Attilio, Robert (reference: Sacco-Vanzetti) (Box 13)
  - Daughters of Bilitis (Box 13)
  - Davies, Katherine (Box 13)
  - Davis, Horace B. (sale of political pamphlets) (Box 13)
  - Davis, Jim (reference: Contemporary History Project) (Box 13)
  - Davis, Peter (re: cooperatives) (Box 14)
  - Davis, Rodney O. (reference: Henry Vincent) (Box 14)
  - Dawley, Alan (reference: Knights of Labor, 8-hour movement) (Box 14)
  - Dawn Press (Box 14)
  - Dawson, Michael (reference: African Blood Brotherhood) (Box 14)
  - Day, Hem (Box 14)
  - Dealbar (Sao Paolo) (Box 14)
  - Dearborn, Mary (reference: Louise Bryant, Art Young) (Box 14)
  - Deboo, Jeffrey ( (Box 14)
  - Deceno, Carlos (reference: gays in Latin America) (Box 14)
  - Dede, Bonnie (Box 14)
  - Deep Ecologist (Australia) (Box 14)
  - Defenders of the American Constitution ( Task Force) (Box 14)
  - Defense de l’Homme (France) (Box 14)
  - DeLeon, David (reference: American anarchism) (Box 14)
  - DeLeon, Solon (Box 14)
  - DeLeonist, The (New York) (Box 14)
  - Dellinger, David (from ECW; no reply) (Box 14)
  - Deminoff, William (reference: Mary Herma Aikin) (Box 14)
  - Demeril, Sinan (re: William F. Ringle collection) (Box 14)
  - Demokatia (New York) (Box 14)
  - Dennison, Elizabeth J. (reference: Russian anarchists in exile) (Box 14)
  - Densmore, Kathleen (reference: Maxion Lieber, Felix Morrow, Robert Cantwell) (Box 14)
  - Denton, Richard (reference: general) (Box 14)
  - DePastino, Todd (reference: Rebel Voices, IWW, Hobohemia) (Box 14)
  - DeShazo, Peter C. (reference: IWW in Chile) (Box 14)
  - Desperate Living (Baltimore, MD) (Box 14)
  - Despite Everything (Berkeley, CA) (Box 14)
  - Despres, Leon M. (Box 14)
  - Destiny Magazine (MA) (Box 14)
  - Detroit Atheist League (Box 14)
  - Detroit Historical Society (reference: Samuel Goldwater) (Box 14)
  - Detroit Labor News (Box 14)
  - Detroit Public Library (Box 14)
  - Deveney, John (reference: Free Love Movement) (Box 14)
  - DeWitt, Miriam Hapgood (reference: Hutchins Hapgood) (Box 14)
  - DeYoung Press (Hull, IA) (Box 14)
  - Dialogue (Ottawa, Canada) (Box 14)
  - Dialogue on Liberty (Sterling, VA) (Box 14)
  - Diament, Ann Lewin (Box 14)
  - Diamond, Dan (Box 14)
  - Diario Las Americas (Miami, FL) (Box 14)
  - Dickinson, Z. Clark (Box 14)
  - Diedrich, Maria (reference: Ottilie Assing and Frederick Douglass) (Box 14)
  - Dierenfield, Bruce J. (reference: Student Peace Union) (Box 14)
  - Dieterich, H.R. (reference: George Herron) (Box 14)
  - Dietz, Kathleen M. (reference: SCLC) (Box 14)
  - Diez, Angel (Box 14)
  - Diez, Lain (re: publications from Chile) (Box 14)
  - Diggins, John P. (reference: Carlo Tresca) (Box 14)
  - Diggs, Alfred (Box 14)
  - Dilgard, David (reference: Everett massacre, Walker C. Smith) (Box 14)
  - Dillingsham, Beth (re: E. Haldeman-Julius donation) (Box 14)
  - Dill, Robert (re: San Diego State U’s Daily Aztec, 1970 student protests) (Box 14)
  - DiMango, Angelo (Italian anarchists in the U.S., Arturo Giovanitti) (Box 14)
  - Dinse, John (reference: New Left) (Box 14)
  - Diplomat Magazine (Chicago) (Box 14)
  - Direct Action (Austalia) (Box 14)
  - Direct Action (Manchester, England) (Box 14)
  - Direct Action (Voluntown, CT) (Box 14)
  - Direkte Aktion (Cologne, West Germany) (Box 14)
  - Discussion Bulletin (Grand Rapids, MI) (Box 14)
  - Distant Drummer (Philadelphia) (Box 14)
  - Dixon Line (Los Alamitos, CA) (Box 14)
  - Dixon, Mary (re: Kill Your Television) (Box 14)
  - Dixon, R. A. N. (reference: Francisco Franco, Juan March) (Box 14)
  - Dobbs, Bill (re: Stonewall 25, LGBT history) (Box 14)
  - Dobbs, John (Box 14)
  - Dock of the Bay (San Francisco, CA) (Box 14)
  - Documents Anarchistes (France) (Box 14)
  - Dodd, George (re: Human Rights Party) (Box 15)
  - Doherty, Bob (Box 15)
  - Dolgin, Erica Lynn (re: Black Legion) (Box 15)
  - Dollar Hollar (Box 15)
  - Dollars & Sense (Somerville, MA) (Box 15)
  - Domanski, Olga (Box 15)
  - Dommergues, Paulette Schubert (reference: Black Nationalist movements) (Box 15)
  - Donaldson, Randall (reference: Robert Reitzel) (Box 15)
  - Donnen, James W.(reference: Alexander Berkman) (Box 15)
  - Donohue, Cathy (reference: labor interest in the development of cooperatives) (Box 15)
  - Door (San Diego) (Box 15)
  - Dorsch Memorial Library/Monroe County Library System (Box 15)
  - Dorsey, David F. (Box 15)
  - Dougherty, Richard M. (Box 15)
  - Dove, The (Central Valley, NY) (Box 15)
  - Dover Publications (Box 15)
  - Draper, Hal (Box 15)
  - Draper, Theodore (Box 15)
  - Draper, Timothy Dean (reference: general) (Box 15)
  - Drews, Cristina (Box 15)
  - Drinnon, Richard (reference: Emma Goldman) (Box 15)
  - Drum (Philadelpha) (Box 15)
  - Drummer (Philadelphia) (Box 15)
  - Duberman, Martin (reference: Paul Robeson) (Box 15)
  - Dubin, Barbara (reference: Josiah Warren; Peaceful Revolutionist) (Box 15)
  - DuBois, Paul Z. (reference: Paul Leicester Ford (Box 15)
  - Dubose, Herman (Box 15)
  - Duke University (re: donation of Socialist Party materials) (Box 15)
  - Dumpster Times (Akron, OH) (Box 15)